{
	"questions": [
			{"question": "Yes I have.", "correct": "true"},
			{"question": "Yes, I've got.", "correct": "false"},
			{"question": "No I haven't.", "correct": "true"},
			{"question": "Yes I've got one.", "correct": "true"},
			{"question": "No I don't.", "correct": "true"},
			{"question": "No, I don't have one.", "correct": "true"},
			{"question": "No, I don't get one.", "correct": "false"},
			{"question": "Yes, I have one.", "correct": "true"},
			{"question": "No I don't have.", "correct": "false"},
			{"question": "No I haven't got.", "correct": "false"},
			{"question": "No I haven't got one.", "correct": "true"}
	]
}